const theme_Questions = [
  [
    { id: 1, title: "Order Status" },
    {
      id: 2,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "How will I know my order was successful?",
      answer:
        "When your order and payment go through, you will be directed to a confirmation page and all is good! You will also receive a confirmation email with all your order details.",
    },

    {
      id: 3,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "Will I be kept informed of the status of my order?",
      answer:
        "As soon as your order and payment go through, we'll send you an order confirmation email. We'll also email you once your order ships (1-5 business days, depending on the selected shipping speed) with a shipping confirmation email with tracking details (applicable in most countries).",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 4, title: "Payment" },
    {
      id: 5,
      idTitle: 4,
      question: "When will ise ethe payment reflected in my account?",
      answer:
        "Once an order is successfully placed, a pending charge is placed on your Credit or Debit card account. Payments are finalized upon shipment per unit shipped. Other payment methods are finalized when the order is placed.",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      idTitle: 4,
      question: "Where do I enter my promo code?",
      answer:
        "If you are trying to use a promo code, you will be prompted to enter it on the payment page at checkout. Look for where it says 'Add a Promo Code.'",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      idTitle: 4,
      question: "Do your prices include sales tax?",
      answer:
        "Our webshop prices do not include sales tax, but tax amount will be listed at checkout and included in the final sale amount.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 8, title: "Changes e cancellations" },
    {
      id: 9,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "Can I make a change to my order?",
      answer:
        "Changes are not possible after your order has been placed. However, there is a small window to cancel your order before it is sent to the warehouse for processing. If you wish to cancel, please submit your request via our On Chatbot (applicable in most countries). This only applies to orders placed with our free shipping option.",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "Can I change my delivery address?",
      answer:
        "Address changes are not possible after your order has been placed. However, there is a small window to cancel your order before it is sent to the warehouse for processing. If you wish to cancel, please submit your request via our On Chatbot (applicable in most countries). This only applies to orders placed with our free shipping option. If the cancellation request is unsuccessful, the best way to update a delivery address is to reach out to the carrier directly. If the carrier is unable to re-route your parcel, it's typically returned to our warehouse after an unsuccessful delivery.",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      idTitle: 8,
      question: "How Can I cancel my order",
      answer:
        "There is a small window after your order is placed to allow for cancellations before the order is sent to the warehouse for processing. If you wish to cancel, please submit your request via our On Chatbot (applicable in most countries)! This only applies to orders placed with our free shipping option.",
    },
  ],

  [
    { id: 12, title: "Order Type" },
    {
      id: 13,
      idTitle: 12,
      question: "Can I order On products in bulk in the webshop?",
      answer:
        "We do not allow for bulk orders to be placed in the webshop, but we are happy to discuss bulk orders on a case by case basis. Speak with a Happiness Deliverer via our Contact Us form to see if we are able to help you out. Please note, products purchased over our website cannot be resold.",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      idTitle: 12,
      question: "Can I order product to or from another country?",
      answer:
        "So long as international transactions are enabled with your bank, you can order from any country! However, the shipping address must be within that location's shipping capabilities. The US warehouse can only ship to US shipping addresses for example. If a shipping address is not eligible, you will not be able to complete checkout.",
    },
  ],

  [
    { id: 15, title: "Acount" },
    {
      id: 16,
      idTitle: 15,
      question:
        "If I want order On shoes online, do I have to open an account?",
      answer:
        "No, you don't need to create a customer account to complete your purchase; you can choose to check out as a guest if you wish. Creating a customer account allows you to view your order history and, most importantly, make purchases for our Last Season or Limited Edition products.",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      idTitle: 15,
      question:
        "I have an account but i forgot the password, whta should I do?",
      answer:
        "No worries. Simply visit the login page here and click on 'forgot password.' We'll send you a new password to your email, and you'll be all set.",
    },
  ],
];

export default theme_Questions;
